freebiejeebies.co.uk 2008-06-19

# 

**Privacy Policy:**  
We are committed to providing both clients and end-users with the utmost in privacy and security. We abide by all industry guidelines and consistently monitor our management and operating methods in order to maintain our valued reputation and integrity. This is our promise to our clients, and end-users.

**Type of Information Collected**  
Freebiejeebies.co.uk is a site offering free products. Information is collected from the consumer through an online form. Applicants submit their name, address, title, e-mail address, and age along with other demographic information and optional questions chosen by the advertiser.

**Use of Collected Information**  
Information is collected by Freebiejeebies.co.uk but is the sole property of the advertiser and is shared only with the advertiser. Each advertiser individually controls what is done with the information collected. We host ads and collect the information from consumers on behalf of our client. We only use this information to audit accuracy. We guarantee unique users to our clients.

**Cookies**  
Cookies are only used to keep track of log-in names and passwords. A user's e-mail address is automatically logged in when they revisit the site and they do not have to re-enter profile information. This is to keep track of preferences and to better tailor the site to the visitor's needs while providing the most effective service to our clients. Information such as IP address internal session ID, user's domain, type of Internet browser, domain of Web site are collected and used only for traffic auditing and analysing trends.

**Delete/Deactivate**  
"Deactivating" refers to the process by which Personally Identifiable Information, upon request, is removed. Because of backups and records of deletions, it may be impossible to delete a consumer's entry without some residual information. An individual who requests to have Personally Identifiable Information deactivated will be functionally deleted. We will not sell, transfer, or use the information relating to a deleted individual in any way. To deactivate your account, please create a support ticket on Freebiejeebies.co.uk

**Correct and Update Information**  
Personal information collected through Freebiejeebies.co.uk may be corrected or updated through various methods. All information must be updated by contacting Freebiejeebies.co.uk staff either through e-mail or postal mail. All changes may be sent to Freebiejeebies.co.uk by creating a support ticket.

**Notification Of Changes**  
In the event that there is a change in the privacy practices of Freebiejeebies.co.uk, all members of Freebiejeebies.co.uk will be contacted via the e-mail address on record. If this e-mail address is not valid, a written notice will be sent to the street address on record.

**Contact Information**  
Freebiejeebies.co.uk, abides by the laws and guidelines of the Internet. We welcome any enquiries as to the use of collected information and cookies, product capabilities, or company methods and practices. If you have any questions, comments or corrections regarding personally identifiable information obtained through us, please e-mail support@freebiejeebies.co.uk
